<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Documentation on Jordy Ruiz</title>
    <link>https://dune-jr.github.io/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Documentation on Jordy Ruiz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dune-jr.github.io/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Building PathFinder</title>
      <link>https://dune-jr.github.io/docs/building_pathfinder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dune-jr.github.io/docs/building_pathfinder/</guid>
      <description>The following contains instructions to get a working PathFinder build. PathFinder only runs on Linux.
Downloading PathFinder You can get the sources over at Github, or use this direct link to the ZIP archive.
Requirements bam PathFinder uses the bam build system. Get it from Github or install the Debian package:
 apt-get install bam  OTAWA Get it at http://otawa.fr/. You will need OTAWA v2. If you run into trouble with dependencies on Debian, I suggest using</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Documentation</title>
      <link>https://dune-jr.github.io/docs/docs_pathfinder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dune-jr.github.io/docs/docs_pathfinder/</guid>
      <description>Documentation for PathFinder&amp;rsquo;s public classes can be generated by running doxygen at the root of the installation directory.
The Classes Index document is located at autodoc/classes.html.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running PathFinder</title>
      <link>https://dune-jr.github.io/docs/running_pathfinder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dune-jr.github.io/docs/running_pathfinder/</guid>
      <description>The following contains instructions for the usage of PathFinder. You will find the pathfinder binaries at the root of the install folder.
Basic use Calls to PathFinder must follow the pathfinder [OPTIONS] PROGRAM [FUNCTION] pattern. Options can be nested as long as they are one letter. Example:
pathfinder -3pa benchmarks/if_then_else_2seq.elf  Abstract interpretation modules PathFinder comes with three abstract interpretation modules, named by their chronological order of development. Older versions are kept for academic interest.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>